export const data=[
    {
        question:"Which property sets different font",
        option1:"font",
        option2:"font-text",
        option3:"font-family",
        option4:"font-size",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Which tag is used to define table row",
        option1:"<td>",
        option2:"<tr>",
        option3:"<th>",
        option4:"<table>",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"We cannot give negative values for - ",
        option1:"Padding",
        option2:"Margin",
        option3:"Both",
        option4:"None",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"h1 {___ : value}",
        option1:"property",
        option2:"something",
        option3:"id",
        option4:"class",
        ans:1,
    },
    {
        question:"How many ways CSS can be written ?",
        option1:"1",
        option2:"2",
        option3:"3",
        option4:"4",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Choose the paired tag from the below",
        option1:"<br>",
        option2:"<tr>",
        option3:"<hr>",
        option4:"<img>",
        ans:2,
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following css property allows elements to be offset, rotated, scaled, and skewed in a variety of different ways",
        option1:"transform-3D",
        option2:"transform-2D",
        option3:"transform-origin",
        option4:"transform",
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:"Internal CSS uses ?",
        option1:"style",
        option2:"style attribute",
        option3:"style tag",
        option4:"None",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:"Highest Specificity",
        option1:"Inline",
        option2:"ID",
        option3:"Class ",
        option4:"!important",
        ans:4,
    },
    {
        question:"The CSS border property specifies the style, color, and ___ of an element's border",
        option1:"length",
        option2:"size",
        option3:"width ",
        option4:"area",
        ans:3,
    },
];